Finding Aid for the Ralph Story Papers LSC.0867
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 1. Broadcasting -- Radio and Television
  - Television, Serial Programs, 1959 - 1982
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.56 - 60, 1965 March 23 - 1965 April 20 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      No.56 Harrison Gray Otis and the bombing of the Los Angeles Times or labor vs. management in Los Angeles in 1910. 1965 March 23. no.57 Teaching youngsters to drink in school; from chuck wagons to catering trucks; the French Hospital. 1965 March 30. no.58 The roller-skate, skateboard, ball throwing law breakers; the Norwegian Seaman's Church in San Pedro; retirement of the nations oldest computer. 1965 April 6. no.59 Americans and their pets - a survey; rassling; the slaughter of Easter pets. 1965 April 13. no.60 Billboard art; Mrs. Louise Peete - murderess. 1965 April 20.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.61 - 65, 1965 April 27 - 1965 May 25 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      No.61 Hollywood markets; cows in Los Angeles county vs. housing developers; the Olympian Hotel - a Los Angeles sports center. 1965 April 27. no.62 Why do we celebrate Mother's Day - a survey; the stagecoach and their drivers in Southern California; private armies. 1965 May 4. no.63 Earthquakes; steam engine cars and the Steam Car Club. 1965 May 11. no.64 Motion picture studio tours; the Bryne report on U.C.L.A. trams. 1965 May 18. The great guitar revival; Chinese fortune cookie business. 1965 May 25.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.66 - 70, 1965 June 1 - 1965 June 29 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      No.66 Golfers gripes; Los Angeles National Air Racers; animal bites in Los Angeles. 1965 June 1. no.67 The Alexandria hotel's secret wing; Hollywood extras and Central Casting; Rincon Island. 1965 June 8. no.68 Diets - a survey; famous names and landmarks in California; the People's World; Latin and the high school Latin Club. 1965 June 15. no.69 Claire Falkenstein's Federal Building fountain - a survey; Los Angeles mayors; rapid transit and the Pacific Electric Red Car line. 1965 June 22. no.70 Santa Claus Programs Inc.; Benjamin Bugsy Siegal, Mickey Cohen, and gangsters in Los Angeles; swallows return to Capistrano (repeat). 1965 June 29.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.71 - 75, 1965 July 6 - 1965 September 19 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      No.71 The grunion survey (repeat); Trooper the Los Angeles Police Department's horse; Edwin Cowston and his ostrich farm; the American Federation of Musicians and their Los Angeles specialists. 1965 July 6. no.72 Where kids get their money - a survey; the haunted history of Griffith Park and the Feliz Adobe (repeat); Manhattan Beach street-lights. 1965 July 13. no.73 That let-down feeling - a survey; Henry Gaylord Wilshire and his boulevard (repeat); the bicycle and cycling in Los Angeles. 1965 July 20. no.74 Santa Monica's Muscle Beach and their musclemen; animal actors in Hollywood. 1965 September 12. no.75 Pigeons in Los Angeles; Allan Hancock and his park (see also no.6); the definition of culture- a survey. 1965 September 19.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.76 - 80, 1965 September 26 - 1965 October 24 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      No.76 The bagel war; zoot-suit, symbol of trouble. 1965 September 26. no.77 Mrs. Mimi Boomhower - a famous missing person; Collis P. Huntington, Santa Monica, the Santa Monica Pier. 1965 October 3. no.78 The Burbank Theater; burlesque in Los Angeles; our ocean: north, south, east or west? 1965 October 10. no.79 Llano del Rio, Calif. - Job Harriman's utopia; Robert O. Jones - organ grinder; what the kids do during the summer - a survey. 1965 October 17. no.80 California mission bells; the post office's rogues gallery; the new car season and the Los Angeles auto show. 1965 October 24.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- 81 - 85, 1965 October 31 - 1965 November 28 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      No.81 The most offensive comic strip characters - a survey; Will Mulholland and the St. Francis dam break, 1928; Document Disintegration Inc. 1965 October 31. no.82 The Santa Ana winds, et al.; California State College at Palos Verdes. 1965 November 7. no.83 Girl Scouts; Dick Fellows - stagecoach robber. 1965 November 14. no.84 [UNK] to unlock the restroom doors of the West Covina D.M.V.; Boyle Heights; Medley Manufacturing Company; slot machine banks and the law. 1965 November 21. no.85 The Session's house - Beverly Hills' potentially haunted house; courtroom dramas and jury duty; Roger Steele's military curio shop; rain in Los Angeles. 1965 November 28.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.86 - 90, 1965 December 5 - 1965 January 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      No.86 The oldest bartender's school; W.K. Kellogg, his Arabian horses and Cal Poly; soap operas a survey. 1965 December 5. no.87 Federal land in Southern California; skywriting; Mrs. Holtgrew - a corn popper. 1965 December 12. no.88 The Terminal Island Freeway; Brinks Incorporated; Bolsa Chica Gun Club. 1965 December 19. no.89 Recapitulation of Ralph Story's Los Angeles in 1965. 1965 December 26. no.90 Clifford Jones, Kenneth Walker and their Bellehurst project; Felix Peano's Door of Life. 1965 January 2.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.91 - 95, 1966 January 9 - 1966 February 6 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      No.91 Commercial advertising - a survey; Barney Oldfield and race car tracks and drivers; M.F. Chapman and chinchilla breeding. 1966 January 9. no.92 Extra-ordinary landmarks that disrupted traffic-- witch's house and pink whale; Sierra Southern Railroad trams; the Bradbury Building. 1966 January 16. no.93 The doctor's image; Elias Jackson Baldwin; smog experiments. 1966 January 23. no.94 The worst drivers - a survey; the DC-3; peep shows and building projects. 1966 January 30. no.95 David Wark Griffith - movie maker. 1966 February 6.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no. 96 - 100, 1966 February 13 - 1966 March 13 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      No.96 The Hollywood Museum; correction and apology to Mr. Kenneth Walker regarding show no.90; weathermen. 1966 February 13. no.97 The best car ever designed - a survey; car makes and models; George Barris and Les Tompkins, and Kustom City; review of the Battle of Los Angeles (see no.52 & 55); Bruno Koglin the Good Humor veteran. 1966 February 20. no.98 Los Angeles Airport's agricultural program; Santa Anita Race Track research; Chester Place - the most exclusive area in Los Angeles. 1966 February 27. no.99 People who had their name in the newspaper and why - a survey; Robert Chess the 10 year old newspaper publisher; our palm trees; Angels Flight cable car. 1966 March 6. no.100 Distinguished guests in Los Angeles have no official place to stay; elevators in Los Angeles; Grauman's Chinese Theater; ferry boats. 1966 March 13.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.101 - 105, 1966 March 20 - 1966 April 17 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      No.101 Balboa Island auto ferry; one last ferry boat - the Sacramento. 1966 March 20. no.102 Los Angeles City Hall floor levels; Signal Hill; national television tests. 1966 March 27. no.103 More on smog; John Dillinger's passenger car, and the Kienholz exhibit; going shopping with Patricia Beal a hired spy. 1966 April 3. no.104 Show business and politics; experiment in international co-existence in the backroom of a famous restaurant; Jungle Jim Shapiro. 1966 April 10. no.105 Long Beach - the senior citizen's haven; the Long Beach Municipal Market; Riverside Rancho - horse haven; Governor Brown on artichokes. 1966 April 17.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.106 - 110, 1966 April 24 - 1966 May 22 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      No.106 John B. Leonis and Vernon, California; a harpsichord factory and muffler shop in Silverlake. 1966 April 24.no.107 Westwood and Le Drogue Store; The Big White Steamer and her predecessors. 1966 May 1. no.108 The worth of wives - a survey; California State Police; the New York Stock Exchange's possible move to Los Angeles; convertible cars in Los Angeles. 1966 May 8. no.109 The golfer's lottery; Elsinore Navel and Military School; Barney's Beanery. 1966 May 15. no.110 The Hollywood Canteen during the war; Herman Goering's 1937 Horch at Carson High School in Torrance; Mr. Killion and others on the list of Disaster Acting Governors. 1966 May 22.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.111 - 115, 1966 May 29 - 1966 July 3 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      No.111 The importance of breakfast - a survey; Exposition Park; Steve Lein and his British, Dutch, French, Spanish and American brigantine. 1966 May 29. no.112 What's heaven?- a survey; Amboy Crater, California. 1966 June 5. no.113 Chinatown. 1966 June 12. no.114 Craig Sinclair's Rolls Royce and Bentley babysitting job; Plant no.3 of the Northrop Norair division in Hawthorne; Felix Peano's Door of Life (repeat); quips on Look magazine's article on California. 1966 June 26. no.115 Total design and not so total design in Los Angeles offices; Hibbard Rankin and family. 1966 July 3.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.116 - 120, 1966 July 10 - 1966 September 18 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      No.116 What people will read this summer (1966) - a survey; Trooper the L.A.P.D.'s horse (repeat); Chumash Indians. 1966 July 10. no.117 Joe Jost's caf?, pool-room, barber-shop and tavern; the hamburger in California. 1966 July 17. no.118 Kids, summer vacation and the Virginia Country Theater; Max Schumacher (repeat). 1966 July 24. no.119 MOS Greatest athlete in history; lawn bowling; Anacapa Island. 1966 September 11. no.120 union Oil refinery; Mission Inn, Riverside. 1966 September 18.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.121 - 125, 1966 September 25 - 1966 October 23 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      No.121 MOS most enjoyable fragrance; Purex Soap Co.; Anaheim. 1966 September 25. no.122 MOS Should older women marry younger men?; Dory fishermen; bottle and can sculpture. 1966 October 2. no.123 Foster Park revisited; oil islands, Long Beach; Falcon Studios, fencing school. 1966 October 9. no.124 Vacant laundry building, Beverly Hills; pre- Columbian art; MOS Peruvian piracy. 1966 October 16. no.125 Rudolph Valentino's boat; Point Mugu space fair and naval missile testings; taxidermy. 1966 October 23.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.126 - 130, 1966 October 30 - 1966 November 27 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      No.126 Will Rogers. 1966 October 30. no.127 MOS sexy movies, Sawtelle VA center, ducks. 1966 November 6. no.128 Vittorio Ludovico Regina and his O Sole Mio caf?; Los Angeles's sister cities; Upland College. 1966 November 13. no.129 M.U.Z.A.K.; Highland Park - history and personalities.1966 November 20. no.130 Los Angeles Firehouse no.13; Judson Studios - creators of stained glass. 1966 November 27.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.131 - 135, 1966 December 4 - 1967 January 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      No.131 Joe Reinisch - lifeguard at White Point; Democrat Springs, California; James Irvine and his ranch. 1966 December 4. no.132 How to remove bumper stickers - a survey; the Sunset Strip; Jim Cooper - news correspondent from Orange County. 1966 December 11. no.133 Christmas Tree forest in the City of Commerce; Mitchell Caverns; the Bank of Cathay. 1966 December 18. no.134 Marble playing in Los Angeles; Caltech and the Rose Bowl; Mr. Tony Spiesman - a telephone operator. 1966 December 25. no.135 U.S. Post Office's terminal annex in Los Angeles; burglary and Signal Alarm Devices; New Years and New Years resolutions - a solution. 1967 January 1.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.136 - 140, 1967 January 8 - 1967 February 5 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      No.136 The largest floating crane in the world; Toluca Lake; the Big Four at Santa Anita. 1967 January 8. no.137 Runaways; Fort MacArthur; the drive from Long Beach to Terminal Island. 1967 January 15. no.138 Sand; Magnolia High School and marine biology as taught aboard the Jet; Thelma Todd's mysterious death. 1967 January 22. no.139 Pet cemeteries; Culver City; the ideal age in history - a survey; satellite resorts. 1967 January 29. no.140 Al Carter- professional assembler of do-it-yourself items; Fred Cairo - pyrotechnician; Jake Stewart - mayor of Huntington Beach and moonlighter; quips on want ads seeking the British. 1967 February 5.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.141 - 145, 1967 February 19 - 1967 March 19 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      No.141 How many drinks are excessive - a survey; drinking in Los Angeles; Bugatti automobiles; Laguna Beach's Pyne Castle. 1967 February 19. no.142 Hangings in effigy; Ralph Hamlin - Los Angeles pioneer automobile dealer; carwashes and cow washes. 1967 February 26. no.143 Fountain of the World cult; Mrs. Hicks and the Lang museum. 1967 March 5. no.144 Better junk stores; skin diving and the Underwater Technology Institute. 1967 March 12. no.145 The American banjo; Laguna Beach; when to travel - a survey. 1967 March 19.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.146- 150, 1967 March 26 - 1967 May 7 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      No.146 Mack Sennett. 1967 March 26. no.147 Bank of A. Levy; Coachella Valley date palms. 1967 April 16. no.148 Africa, U.S.A.; National Bobby Sock Softball League; people and poly-unsaturates - a survey. 1967 April 23. no.149 Captains Roost on Mount Hollywood; Air California and housewives; schools, school bonds, etc. 1967 April 30. no.150 Courtney C. Julian, Sheridan C. Lewis, Jacob Berman; Addison Loomis - underwater painter. 1967 May 7.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.151 - 155, 1967 May 14 - 1967 June 11 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      No.151 How many credit cards should an ordinary citizen carry? - a survey; Zane Grey; pretzel factory. 1967 May 14. no.152 Salt-water fishing and the Tuna Club; sport fishing; Cannery Row at Newport Beach. 1967 May 21. no.153 Weddings - a survey; Green Hotel, Pasadena; William S. Hart County Park and the buffalo problem. 1967 May 28. no.154 The Coca Cola Bottling Company of Los Angeles; the Y.W.C.A. of Los Angeles; Sleepy Hollow, California; MOS tickets. 1967 June 4. no.155 Roy Stunger, et. Al., Creative blacksmiths; Alhambra Foundry Company, Limited; kids describing their fathers - a survey. 1967 June 11.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.156 - 160, 1967 June 18 - 1967 July 16 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      No.156 American Legion Post Seven-Ninety-Six in Topanga Canyon and beatniks, teeny-boppers, hippies, and flower children in the area. 1967 June 18. no.157 How important is a suntan - a survey; Olympic Village; Christy Duca - Dodger Stadium grounds keeper and the Rainbow Worm Farm. 1967 June 25. no.158 When you stroll, carry identification; Lookout Mountain's movie makers; modern shepherds. 1967 July 2. no.159 Tommy Koulax - restaurant tycoon; automated radio station KTBT and its helpers; Edward H. Bohlin - artist and creator of western gear. 1967 July 9. no.160 The common cold - a survey; speleology; Mitchell Caverns (repeat); Long Beach citizens and their electric carts. 1967 July 16.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.161 -165, 1967 July 23 - 1967 October 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      No.161 Los Angeles harbor - history; Frank Taylor and other new and used car dealers. 1967 July 23. no.162 Alice Marble - champion tennis player, etc; poems people had to memorize - a survey. 1967 September 10. no.163 MOS favorite candy; Mary See's candies; band concerts especially in Long Beach. 1967 September 17. no.164 people's most embarrassing moments - a survey; The Del Mar Hotel; Newport Harbor; Herman Goering's yacht. 1967 September 24. no.165 Japanese-Americans and Little Tokyo. 1967 October 1.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.166 - 168, 1967 October 8 - 1967 October 22 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      No.166 Sky Dunlap's Pacific Clipping Service; Sol Munn - picture framer; the Battle of La Mesa. 1967 October 8. no.167 Actor's Studio West; William S. Hart. 1967 October 15. no.168 What the 11th commandment should be - a survey; Clifford Clinton and his cafeterias; bird watching at the Proud Bird. 1967 October 22.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.169 - 173, 1967 October 29 - 1967 November 26 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      No.169 The Cleveland Wrecking Company; the Buffalo Soldiers of the Tenth Cavalry. 1967 October 29. no.170 Should ordinary citizens keep and use firearms - a survey in Pasadena; the Eastern Firearms Corps; chimney sweeps. 1967 November 5. no.171 Upton Sinclair; irritating habits - a survey. 1967 November 12. no.172 Sonny Yates - a blind sky-diver; David Koeningsberg - an 11 year old producer; roofs in Los Angeles. 1967 November 19. no.173 Ethel Meglin and the Meglin Kiddies; people and their favorite song - a survey. 1967 November 26.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.174 - 177, 1967 December 3 - 1967 December 24 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      No.174 Who's fault is the cost of living problem? - a survey; Los Angeles Trade Technical College; Santa Monica City College; the Santa Monica College Coronettes. 1967 December 3. no.175 Palm tree growing in the Hollywood freeway; the many faces of segregation; should young and old live together - a survey; the Carmichael family of Pasadena - all four generations. 1967 December 10. no.176 Pasadena and New Year's Day, Rose Parade; Cal State Long Beach's International Investigations Systems; lady detectives. 1967 December 17. no.177 Round House George Lehman, Jack Kent Cooke and the Forum; jockey school. 1967 December 24.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.178 - 182, 1967 December 31 - 1968 January 28 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      No.178 Year end recap, quips and added comments on previous Ralph Story's Los Angeles shows. 1967 December 31. no.179 Cabazon, Calif. Where gambling is legal; school bullies - a survey. 1968 January 7. no.180 Would you put a coin in a parking meter to save somebody else a ticket?- a survey; Union Ice and other ice companies; Hermosa Reptile Company. 1968 January 14. no.181 Are movie prices too high? - a survey; Ed Mann - a non-Irish piper; the Volkswagen and Doyle, Dane, Bernbach Advertising Company. 1968 January 21. no.182 Dentists, dentistry, USC School of Dentistry and Dental Health Week; natural gas tanks. 1968 January 28.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.183 - 186, 1968 February 4 - 1968 February 25 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      No.183 Hollywood Ranch Market; computer tape laundry. 1968 February 4. no.184 Los Angeles at night. 1968 February 11. no.185 Olvera Street and Christine Sterling; U.C.L.A. Folklore and Mythology Center; stories parents tell children to make them behave - a survey. 1968 February 18. no.186 The Venice trams; Wil-Form Buggy Works; Sulky factory. 1968 February 25.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.187 - 189, 1968 March 3 - 1968 March 17 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      No.187 Unnecessary clothing - a survey; tortillas in Los Angeles; the Japanese Kendo; more on the palm tree in the Hollywood Freeway (see no.175). 1968 March 3. no.188 Grama (Tressa) Prisbey - collector, bottle village; conversion of city dumps; waste management in Los Angeles. 1968 March 10. no.189 John Musante - traveling greengrocer Bel Air; springs and spas and Bimini Baths. 1968 March 17.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.190 - 194, 1968 April 7 - 1968 May 12 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      No.190 James J. Jeffries - champion fighter and his barn; the Queen Mary in Long Beach; boring people - a survey. 1968 April 7. no.191 Property and property investments in Los Angeles; Sperling Sales for cannery rejects. 1968 April 21. no.192 Helena Modjeska; identity - a survey. 1968 April 28. no.193 Freeway systems. 1968 May 5. no.194 Bel Air on trash day; jockey school (repeat); Don Bleitz's Wildlife Foundation; hummingbirds; unaired draft about men's fashion. 1968 May 12.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.195 - 200, 1968 May 19 - 1968 June 30 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      No.195 What is a Vamp? - a survey; Hollywood Vamps. 1968 May 19. no.196 Bowie Pie Company; Palm Springs aerial tramway; snobs - a survey. 1968 May 26. no.197 Paul J. Howard's Flowerland; Paul Mancherat DeLongpre - king of the flowers; a trip in the Los Angeles sewers; jobs that are overpaid - a survey. 1968 June 9. no.198 Heroes - a survey; Greer Garson and Los Angeles; airplane crop dusters. 1968 June 16. no.199 The Charles W. Bowers Memorial Museum; the live bait business in Long Beach. 1968 June 23. no.200 People's most exciting and frightening ride - a survey; scary rides in Los Angeles; Del Graham's circus aerialist school. 1968 June 30.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.201 - 205, 1968 July 14 - 1968 September 22 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      no.201 Wrigley Field; beachcombers. 1968 July 14. no.202 Los Angeles Free Press; diaries - a survey. 1968 July 21. no.203 Franciscan pottery; John Windle - constable of Avalon; Pacific Auto Rental. 1968 July 28. no.204 The Thomas Whaley house in San Diego; ghosts - a survey. 1968 September 15. no.205 Sunset Blvd. (see also no.132). 1968 September 22.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.206 - 210, 1968 September 29 -1968 October 27 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      no.206 Snoring - a survey; Harry Ruby - song writer; Roy Ward - truck driver, farmer. 1968 September 29. no.207 Ralph Story's mustache; James Goodhew and his ambulance service; William Mulholland Memorial Fountain. 1968 October 6. no.208 Pampered pets - a survey; John Robert Powers and his modeling schools. 1968 October 13. no.209 Remembered teachers - a survey; Sanford Darling - a very special house painter; clay pigeon shooting; 1924 Pullman rail and cable cars. 1968 October 20. no.210 Palmdale; sentimental objects - a survey; old tires; Alfred Di Mariano - mass producer of religious statuary. 1968 October 27.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.211 - 215, 1968 November 3 - 1968 December 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      No.211 Boston Curtis and other mules; Don Davis, musicologist and his one- man bands. 1968 November 3. no.212 Tiburcio Vasquez - outlaw; horoscopes - a survey. 1968 November 10. no.213 Fashionable restaurants in Los Angeles; Herb's Grill; tombs, graves, graveyards, etc. 1968 November 17. no.214 Zaddie Bunker - pioneer woman; Western Trainer - steers, cow-ponies; smoking- a survey. 1968 November 24. no.215 The Salvation Army; mushroom growing. 1968 December 1.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.216 - 219, 1968 December 8 - 1968 January 19 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      No.216 The olive industry, Sylmar and Cristo Fusano; ornamentation and the Americanization of Los Angeles buildings. 1968 December 8. no.217 Quips on Ralph Story's Los Angeles; Television commercials most hated by the public - a survey; Sabreliner - Mustang - World War II fighter plane; final exams for stewardesses at Jolly Roger restaurant. 1968 December 15. no.218 Boy Scouting; Nudie's Westerner dress shop. 1968 January 12. no.219 Lon Chaney (repeat). 1968 January 19.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.220 - 223, 1968 January 26 - 1969 February 16 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      No.220 The worst movie of 1968 - a survey; stocks, securities and brokerage firms; Mexican and Indian dancing. 1968 January 26. no.221 The kind of boss people would like to work for - a survey; the sea-going squadron of the Los Angeles Fire Department; Van Nuys - Sherman Oaks war memorial told as Wizard of Oz. 1969 February 2. no.222 The City Traffic Department; neon and other signs; Australian gray crickets. 1969 February 9. no.223 Land speculation and housing developments in the Los Angeles area; the eucalyptus tree. 1969 February 16.
    - KNXT Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- no.224 - 227, 1969 February 23 - 1969 March 16 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      No.224 How children make money - a survey; Wolf and Vine Incorporated - mannequin makers; Railroad Passenger Car Washer; San Jacinto, California - site of record non- stop distance plane landing. 1969 February 23. no.225 San Jacinto; MOS banks. 1969 March 2. no.226 Vamps (see no.195). 1969 March 9. no.227 Avocados; Yorba Linda; Poles. 1969 March 16.